http://www.foodbanklarimer.org/privacy-policy

The Food Bank for Larimer County (FBLC) shares your concerns about privacy on the Internet. In order to better protect your privacy the FBLC has provided this notice explaining online and other gathered information practices and how that information is used. FBLC is committed to taking all reasonable steps to ensure that information provided to us is handled in a safe and secure manner. We value your support and are committed to protecting your privacy.
What information do we collect and how do we use it?
When you visit our site, we collect some non-identifying basic information. This includes total number of visitors, pages viewed and other non-identifying information. We use this collective information to improve our site and to make your experience on our web site as smooth as possible.
Donations made online to us are processed through a secure network connection. When you make a donation online, we ask for your name, address, daytime phone, e-mail address, and credit card information. This information is conveyed to FBLC by e-mail from the secure page. We use your credit card number and address to process your donation(s) and to verify credit card data. If the donation is greater than $250.00, we use your mailing address to send you tax-deductible receipts. Your phone number is used to contact you if we need to verify your donation information. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We do not use your phone number to do telephone solicitations.
If you’re not completely comfortable submitting your credit card information online, please call our office at 970.493.4477 or e-mail info@foodbanklarimer.org and we will be happy to help you in any way we can.
You can mail your donation info to:
Food Bank for Larimer County
5706 Wright Drive
Loveland, CO 80538
Does FBLC sell or share donor information & names with other organizations?
No. The only mailing list that your name will be added to is our own. We do work with a third-party provider for mailers but they are for our use only and are not shared with any other organization. From time to time, we may publish donor lists in our annual report and other publications, but do not list addresses or other contact info. If at any time you wish to have your name removed from our mailing list, or prefer not to have your name included in the publications, please contact the Development Department at 970.493.4477 or e-mail info@foodbanklarimer.org and we will be happy to honor your request.
It is the policy of FBLC not to sell, trade, or rent your personal information to anyone. FBLC does not share your information with telemarketing centers. We do not use telephone marketing to solicit donations.
Can you make an anonymous donation?
Yes. You can send anonymous donations simply by sending a money order to us at the address above. If you do not give your name and address we will be unable to send you a tax-deductible receipt. You may also send us a check or credit card info and request your name be anonymous and not published.
Can you opt out of mailing list and/or e-communications?
Yes. You may choose not to receive information from us electronically by contacting FBLC directly. We send e-marketing via a third-party provider and upon receipt of an “opt out” request, your name will be removed from future marketing communications. If you choose to no longer receive physical mailings from us, please contact the Development Department at 970.493.4477 or info@foodbanklarimer.org . Upon receipt and processing of your request, we will remove your name and address and you will not receive solicitations, event invitations, and other mailed communications. Please note, we make every attempt to immediately remove your name from our mailing list however, you may receive something after the request has been made due to the advance timing and planning of our direct mail outreach.
Modification of Privacy Policy
The FBLC may change this Privacy Policy at any time and will post the changed or amended Privacy Policy to the site. Your continued viewing of or use of this website following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to any such changes or amendments.
How to contact the Food Bank for Larimer County for any reason
You may contact FBLC with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, updating personally identifiable information, or anything else related to the FBLC and or this Site at www.foodbanklarimer.org or at 970.493.4477.
PagesAbout Us
Agency Zone
Annual Report & Financials
Area Resources
Become a Hunger-Relief Advocate!
Do I Qualify?
how does it work?
Where Do I Go?
The Food Bank for Larimer County is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization recognized by the IRS, ID
74-2336171. All donations are tax-deductible as allowed by law -
info@foodbanklarimer.org.Request a Speaker or Tour
>Tour the Food Bank for Larimer County, or request a speaker for your group.
Online Request FormAgency Zone >Important Updates for our Nonprofit Agency Partners.
Learn More
Scroll to top
